<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Digital Garden</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Digital Garden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a Low-Code/No-Code Data Engineering Framework: A First-Hand Experience - Part I</title>
      <link>/posts/building_nocode_lowcode_data_engineering_part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:01:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/building_nocode_lowcode_data_engineering_part1/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the world of Low-Code/No Code Data Engineering. But before we do, let&amp;rsquo;s set the stage with a bit of context on the Data Engineering Process.
Traditional data engineering is a complex and intricate process. It involves creating and maintaining architectures, databases, and processing systems that deal with vast amounts of data. Think of Data Engineers as the architects of data. They build pipelines that transform and transport data into a format that can be used by data scientists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Visibility - Lessons from &#39;Show Your Work!&#39;</title>
      <link>/posts/show_your_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:51:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/show_your_work/</guid>
      <description>Let me get one thing straight - Austin Kleon&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Show Your Work!&amp;rsquo; has been rattling around in my brain like a catchy pop song for months now. You know the type - it&amp;rsquo;s 3 AM, you&amp;rsquo;re trying to sleep, and all you can hear is &amp;lsquo;share your work, share your work.&amp;rsquo; It&amp;rsquo;s like a mantra, a chant, a nagging parent reminding you to clean your room. but instead of dirty laundry, it&amp;rsquo;s all about airing our your knowledge and learning for the world to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the Journey - Unveiling My Digital Haven</title>
      <link>/posts/why_am_i_blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/why_am_i_blogging/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my digital haven, a place where technology, ideas, and a touch of personal musings intertwine. In this inaugural blog post, I want to share with you the inspiration behind this endeavor, the essence of the quote that sparked it all, and what you can expect from this virtual rendezvous.
A Spark of Inspiration It all started with a glimpse of destiny hidden within the captivating embrace of a Hugo theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
